Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Look here! Stand up!
Stand up! Who are you?
Who are you?
I am a snake.
You are a snake?
Yes!
What have you done to her?
Disappointment.
How? Explain!
I give her discouragements. There is no concentration at school.
I own her.
You as a snake, how did you enter her body?
I entered her body through friends.
Through friends?
Through friends she keeps.
I have a covenant with her.
What kind of covenant?
Tattoo covenant.
Tattoo covenant?
Yes.
Where is that tattoo?
Why are you asking me?
I own her.
You said you have made a tattoo covenant with her.
Yes.
Where is the tattoo?
I have a covenant with her.
It's on her back.
On her back?
Yes.
How many powers do you have inside of her?
I have three powers.
Three powers?
Yes, three powers.
Mention them one by one!
I have on her legs, her two hands, and I use her body.
You use her body?
Yes.
Those tattoos, when I have a covenant with her, she used to dream about me.
I am the snake of the marine spirit.
I am the snake.
The moment, I did the covenant with her, she started working for me.
In what way does she work for you?
She works for me by getting people into my kingdom.
She gets people into your kingdom?
She gets people into my kingdom.
How does she get people for your kingdom?
And soon, I will make her the queen.
How do you take people to your kingdom?
Through my legs when I am walking in the streets.
Whoever that looks at my body also comes to my feet
and when he comes to my feet, I take him to my kingdom.
Okay, walk the way you walk in the streets. Let's see!
They come to my kingdom.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
How many people have you taken to your kingdom so far?
I've taken a lot of people.
How do you use the power in her hands?
The power in my hands, I use it when she's angry. I gave her the spirit of anger.
Whenever she is angry or whenever you try to insult her,
she points her hand at you; then you are in my kingdom.
Okay, any person she points her hand at.
Yes! I use these two fingers.
You use it as what?
This is part of the power I gave her.
I use it to get people for my kingdom.
Every power that I gave her, the three powers that she has,
she uses them to get people for my kingdom.
The power in her legs is also part of her to also get people for my kingdom.
How?
By the way I walk.
You said, the body too has power?
Yes!
How do you use that one?
The body - no one can resist her body.
Look at these people.
Who are these people to you?
I don't know anyone of them.
You don't know them?
Yes, I don't know anyone of them. I came alone.
You came alone?
Yes!
From where? Where did you come from?
Firstly, I came from the sea; she has the spirit of fish.
She can't sleep without putting her legs together
She doesn't sleep on one side; she sleeps straight up.
She sleeps straight up?
Yes!
Ok, show us!
She plays at night. She comes to me.
We play at night in the river with other people in our kingdom there.
We play all together.
Can you show us the way she sleeps at night?
She sleeps like this. This is just the way she sleeps.
Stand up! Now, show us the way she walks!
This is the way she walks, and whenever you look at her legs, you look at her legs, you are in our kingdom.
Move like a snake! Let us see how a snake moves.
Move!
I am a snake. Oh, please, leave me alone.
Now, move like a fish! You said you are also a fish!
Now, stand up! Come here!
What can you say about your sister?
Spirit of fornication is too much
Do you live with her?
I stay with her almost all the time.
What she is saying is true because she has the spirit of anger.
She is always angry.
She is always angry?
It is almost like we are younger than her because she wants to be on top.
You cannot tell her what to do. She will tell you what you will do.
If you don't want to do it, you will stay away.
So, anything she says, you people have to obey it in the house?
Exactly, that's what she wants. That is what she wants us to do all the time.
If you don't obey her, what will happen?
She just gets angry. She might end up not talking to you for one week.
She might be washing dishes and then you come to her and ask her to do something for you.
She would just look at you. I don't know what she saw though.
But she would not do it - as if I was younger than her.
Most of the time when I got back from school, my mother kept complaining
that when she stands, she keeps her feet up like this - she keep her feet tipped on the floor.
My mum keeps asking her to straighten her legs but she doesn't.
Most of the time, she stands like this.
When she sleeps, she sleeps like this, with her right hand upward like this.
My mum would come to knock at my room and say that she keeps her hand upward like this at night.
Okay. Now, you demon, you said that you have destroyed many men.
Yes!
Through fornication
How do you destroy them? What will happen to them?
Any man that sleeps with her, what will happen to the person?
If he used to succeed, his success would be drained - it would go down.
You would be seeing us in your dreams, we would come and torment you.
That is how we work.
I have destroyed a lot of people - every aspect of the society.
Whenever they sleep with me, their businesses will go down.
If you are expecting anything, it will go down
and they will be part of our members. That is how we work.
Now tell us - how many men do you get in a day?
In a day, four or five.
How do you get them?
Whenever she walks in the streets, she gets all the attention.
I gave her the power.
The people that she gets, what class of people are they?
High class people but I want to punish her because she can't have anything close to those people.
I send her to get them for me, and that's it.
The caliber of people I am talking about here are big men.
I don't know the type of business they do.
I want them to come to my world, then I will give them more wealth,
if only they obey me.
Anyone who doesn't want to obey me, they go down.
Everything that has a beginning must have an end. Your end has come in this body.
Now you are going.
In the mighty name of Jesus, out of her! Holy Ghost fire all over your body!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! All over your body! From your head to your toes!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ! Holy Ghost fire!
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Out of her, you demon!
You snake, out!
In Jesus' name!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord, for this deliverance!
You are declared free in the name of Jesus!
Thank You, Lord.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
How are you, sister?
I'm okay.
Who are these people to you?
These are my brothers, and this is my mum.
Okay, you said that you are a snake and a fish.
No, I am not a snake, I am not a fish. I am Princess by name.
Your name is Princess?
Yes.
You listened to that. It means that the person talking before was an evil spirit
and Jesus has cast that evil spirit out.
She is delivered and all those things that she has confessed,
she is not the one responsible for it; it was the demon.
Therefore, you should never for a moment use her confession against her
so that you too will not be tempted.
She is free.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You, Jesus, I am delivered!
Thank You, Jesus, for delivering my family!
STANDARD FOR LIFE
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Princess Obasi.
I am originally from Nigeria but I live in South Africa.
The problem that brought me to The Synagogue Church of All Nations was
that I was possessed with the spirits of snake and fish.
The spirit of snake gave me three powers which I used to initiate people into our kingdom.
They gave me power in my two fingers, legs and in my body as well.
The power I used the most was the power in my legs
because from my waist downwards was a fish
and from my waist upwards was like that of a human being.
They gave me the assignment to go out and bring people into our kingdom
especially men that are of the high class in the society.
If I initiated any man and he became a part of our kingdom,
his finances would go down and he would become a member
and he would go out and get more souls.
When I walked on the streets, the thing that caught men's attention were my legs.
They showed me the way I would walk.
I also made a covenant with a snake which was the tattoo on my back
which was shown on the screen.
You said when you walked on the streets, your legs actually drew attention.
What was in your legs?
There were a lot of powers in my legs - the powers of a fish.
I used it when I walked on the streets to catch the attention of men.
The only men I went out with were men that drive.
If I walked on the streets and you looked at my legs, you would be tempted.
I would stop, we would exchange numbers and meet at a guest house.
Whenever we have sexual intercourse, you would become part of our kingdom.
That was how I worked for those marine spirits.
I had a covenant with them which was the tattoo on my back.
Before I got this tattoo, I had a dream where I was with them.
We are playing the way we usually did in the river.
Whenever I was in the river, you would see part of my body as a fish
but physically, you wouldn't see it as a fish.
Only I knew that a part of my body was a fish.
When we were playing, they told me that they wanted us to have a covenant.
and that was what I would do to make a covenant with them.
They showed me the pattern of the tattoo I would get.
After dreaming, I woke up and I had the urge of getting a tattoo.
I went to where they do tattoos and they brought out patterns of tattoos.
I particularly chose the pattern that they had given me.
I chose the pattern and got the tattoo.
When I got the tattoo, I became their full member.
The power I had in the tattoo was that when any man saw my nakedness
and then saw my tattoo, they would stick to me.
They wouldn't go out there.
Married men's homes would be destroyed because of the evil spirit I had.
What of the beads?
It was also part of the initiation that I had.
It was part of my powers. I got the tattoo before the beads.
I chose the red colour because in my kingdom, red is the colour we like
and that is my favourite colour in real life.
Those three power were the most powerful powers the marine spirits gave me.
Those were the powers that I normally used to work for them.
I had gotten a lot of souls in those years.
They said that at the end of this year, they would make me a queen.
By the grace of God, I was delivered this year from the marine spirit and the spirit of snake.
I am no longer in that kingdom and I am no longer going to be the queen
or whatever they promised to do for me.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Did you have an association where people would come together for a meeting
or did you people purely meet in the spirit?
Yes, there was a physical association, coming together but it was within the friends I kept.
We would do everything together but we wouldn't talk about
what was happening in the spiritual world, when in the physical.
Within us, we didn't know we were in the same kingdom
because we had different works they had given us to do physically.
Did you have particular people you always went for
or you just wanted to get men to your kingdom?
I had particular people that I was directed to.
When I was dream, they would show me the type of people
and how my day would unfold physically.
They would show me what type of men would approach me
and what type of men I would be with.
The type of people that I met in life were high-class business men.
Those were the type of people we wanted.
Whenever I initiated them, they would work for us.
They would receive more wealth.
If you were stubborn and didn't want to work for us, we would take down your finances.
That was how we worked and how I was sent.
That was what the spiritual people would tell me to do.
Every day, I could sleep with four or five men in total.
The evil spirit inside me would confuse you.
We could go to your house or to a guest house
but mostly, we would go to a guest house.
Were you interested in the financial gain apart from spiritual attacks?
You collected money. What was your physical gain apart from the spiritual attacks?
A part of me was interested in the finances.
Another part of me had a different work that I had to do
because that was the spirit they had given me.
I couldn't just wake up in the morning, sleep with a man and come out empty-handed.
That was how the evil spirit worked in my life and destroyed my life.
Personally, it was not your desire to go after men
but there was a force that was pushing you to do so.
Is that what you are trying to say?
Yes, Man of God.
Sometimes, I was not controlled by the evil spirit.
It had times when it would come to me.
When it came to me, I couldn't control myself.
When you were going out the way the spirit used you -
was your mum then aware that you normally went out for men?
No, she did not know.
If I wanted to go out, I would do the house chores.
I would make sure I did everything at home.
When I went out, I would tell her I am going to my friend.
She didn't know where I was really going to.
So, you never did anything for them to suspect?
There was no time that they suspected you were into that business?
Yes, there was a time they suspected. Whenever they talked about it, I got angry.
I had the spirit of stubbornness; I didn't listen to anyone.
When they started talking about it, I knew that what they said was true
but I wouldn't listen to that.
When they started talking about it, I would just walk out.
What is your advice to the youth?
Start by telling the youth what they should guard against.
How did this thing initially come into your life?
If you were aware that something like this was going to ruin your life,
initially, you would not have allowed this to happen.
Could you advise the youth how they can guard against this?
Was it through a friend you contacted this affliction or what?
What can they guard against so that they would not fall into this?
Like I said before - my name is Princess Obasi, and I am 18 years old.
My advice to the youth and teenagers out there is that they should focus on their education.
Listen to your parents because if I knew that such things could happen to me,
I would have never lost concentration in school.
I didn't have concentraion in my studies.
Not that I couldn't listen in school, I could listen and study,
but I had the spirit of distraction. I was normally distracted.
So, my advice to the youth out there is to have faith in God.
If you are suffering from what I suffered from, you should come out
and share your testimony to the Lord and the Lord who delivered me
will also set you free from every evil spirit that has been tormenting you.
Wow!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Okay, what can you say?
You were once in the world and at your age you know better
because in the world today, your age, your class is 90% over there.
They have taken over the whole world.
Can you tell us - are you afraid of the future of this world,
going by what has happened?
Can you tell us about what is happening in the world.
Can you also prophecy and tell us about what you think will likely happen
if we do not pray, concerning the world at large.
Tell us about what is happening in the world.
Now that you are out of the system.
From my aspect of view, I think that this word is full of atrocities, fornication;
a lot of things that are happening are against the Bible.
Sometimes, I would also get confused about my own future
because I had a particular dream of what I wanted to be
but the evil spirit usually pushed me away from my dreams.
I think that what happened to me is happening to every other youth and teenager.
If we don't take time, because of what I have experienced,
I think the world is going to be like Sodom and Gomorrah.
I want a person like her to speak to the world. And she has said it all.
She is saying, if we do not pray to change what is on the board now, it is written already.
With prayer, it can be erased.
She is saying that if intensive prayer is not offered,
the world will turn upside down.
From my own aspect of view, from what I have experienced and seen in the world,
I think that if we are not prayerful and don't take time
this world is going to be like Sodom and Gomorrah.
When I say Sodom and Gormorrah, I mean the aspect of youth going to Facebook.
You can see fathers, married men and women on Facebook.
In every chatroom, you can be initiated into those things.
That was what I meant when I said Sodom and Gomorrah.
You can easily be initiated in those chatrooms.
What I meant when I said Sodom and Gomorrah
was the aspect of facebooking, internet, ponography and chatting.
You can see young people, married men and women putting themselves on Facebook and internet.
Some people are there looking for husband, friendship and dates.
Internet, Facebook, Ekimi, 2go are initiating people as well.
They are initiating you and that is what we are experiencing in this world.
This is what I mean by Sodom and Gomorrah.
That is misusing of those things.
One thing we don't know - as God's children are using those things,
satan's children are also using them.
As you chat on whatever medium you are chatting on,
satan's children also use them to chat.
There is a medium now they can use to capture you.
You will not know the person that you are talking to.
At a time you discover, you realise the person you are talking to, you have gone too far.
A relationship can be too far to disconnect from.
My advice to the world, as I was tormented by the spirits of snake and fish
and was delivered from all the marine sprits that had been tormenting my life,
if God could deliver me, He can also deliver other people with different situations.
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.